Lawrence R. Johnson Missouri Pacific Railroad and Railroad Union Records 6330
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Lawrence R. Johnson Missouri Pacific Railroad and Railroad Union Records
1903-2014
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Johnson, Lawrence R.
Missouri Pacific Railroad (MOPAC)
Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen (BRT)
Order of Railway Conductors (ORC)
United Transportation Union (UTU)
6330
4.33 cubic feet
4.3 linear ft.
Records, photographs.
7541340
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 12, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 31, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6330 MB: Lawrence R. Johnson Missouri Pacific Railroad and Railroad Union Memorabilia 6330 PUBS: Lawrence R. Johnson Missouri Pacific Railroad and Railroad Union Publications
Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions; Johnson, Lawrence R.; Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen; Missouri Pacific Railroad Company; Order of Railway Conductors of America; United Transportation Union
7541340
- Agreements, 1940-1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Agreement: Missouri Pacific Railroad and UTU, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Agreement: Missouri Pacific Railroad and UTU, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Scope and Contents
  Copy 2.
- Arbitration Awards, 1965-1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Strike Clippings, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Strike Clippings, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Soo Line Strike, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Articles and Clippings, 1945-1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- General Grievance Committee, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Brotherhood Relief and Compensation Fund, 1950-1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Lawrence Johnson Retirement, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Photograph (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Not identified. Most likely it is of Mr. Johnson
- Certificates, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Railroad Retirement Board, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Railroad Retirement Board, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Railroad Accident Regulations, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Missouri Pacific Railroad Circular no.81, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Caboose Condition Reports, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Caboose Condition Reports, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Correspondence: Cabooses, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Correspondence: Cabooses, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Correspondence: Cabooses, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Correspondence: Cabooses, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Correspondence: Cabooses, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Correspondence: Cabooses, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Correspondence: Cabooses, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Correspondence: Cabooses, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Correspondence: Cabooses, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Correspondence: Cabooses, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Correspondence: Cabooses, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Correspondence: Cabooses, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Correspondence: Cabooses, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Correspondence: Cabooses, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Correspondence: General, 1944-1958 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Correspondence: General, 1963-1969 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Correspondence: General, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Correspondence: General, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Correspondence: General, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Correspondence: General, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Correspondence: General, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Correspondence: General, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Correspondence: General, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Correspondence: General, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Correspondence: General, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Correspondence: General, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Correspondence: General, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Correspondence: General, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Correspondence: General, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Correspondence: General, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Correspondence: General, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Correspondence: General, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Correspondence: General, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Correspondence: General, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Correspondence: General, 1990-1999 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Correspondence: General (Box 1, Folder 55)
  No date
- Correspondence: Missouri Senators, 1983-2000 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  January
- Time and Delay Reports, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  February
- Time and Delay Reports, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  March
- Time and Delay Reports, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  April
- Time and Delay Reports, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  May
- Time and Delay Reports, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  June
- Time and Delay Reports, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  July
- Time and Delay Reports, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  August
- Time and Delay Reports, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  September
- Time and Delay Reports, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  October
- Time and Delay Reports, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  November
- Time and Delay Reports, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  December
- Time and Delay Reports, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Summary
- Time and Delay Reports, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 75)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 76)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 77)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 79)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 80)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Time and Delay Reports, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Track Warrents, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Rock Island Line Train Orders, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Santa Fe Railroad Train Orders, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Union Pacific Railroad Train Orders, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Missouri Pacific Railroad Train Orders, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Missouri Pacific Railroad Train Orders, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Missouri Pacific Railroad Train Orders, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Missouri Pacific Railroad Train Orders, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Missouri Pacific Railroad Train Orders, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Union Pacific Railroad Train Orders, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Missouri Pacific Railroad Train Orders, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Missouri Pacific Railroad Train Orders, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Missouri Pacific Railroad Train Orders, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Missouri Pacific Railroad Train Orders, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Missouri Pacific Railroad Train Orders, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Missouri Pacific Railroad Train Orders, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Seniority List, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Seniority List, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Seniority List, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Seniority List, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Seniority List, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Seniority List, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Seniority List, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Crew Lists (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Car Pick-Up Form no.29363, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Stationery (Box 3, Folder 46)
  Missouri Pacific Railroad and United Transportation Union envelopes
- Annecdotes (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Delaware and Hudson Canal Company Caboose no.10 Plans and Specifications, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  Two sets: one from Model Railroader Magazine and one from Railroad Model Craftsman Magazine. Both October 1965. This is the caboose where the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen was started in Oneonta, NY, September 1883.
- UTU President Alfred Chesser's 100th Birthday, 2013-2014 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Lawrence Johnson Retirement, 1990-2009 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Lawrence Johnson Insurance, 1975-2007 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Lawrence Johnson Obituary and Memorial, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Photogaphs, 1969-1979 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Order of Railway Conductors Divison 279 Minute Book, 1903-1926 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Lodge 637 Attendance Book, 1913-1925 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Order of Railway Conductors Divison 279 Dues Ledger, 1903-1913 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Order of Railway Conductors Divison 279 Dues Ledger, 1913-1924 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Order of Railway Conductors Divison 279 Dues Ledger, 1925-1933 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Order of Railway Conductors Divison 279 Dues Ledger, 1935-1942 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Lodge 637 Record Book, 1909-1919 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Lodge 637 Record Book, 1920-1927 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Lodge 637 Record Book, 1927-1938 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Lodge 637 Record Book, 1938-1945 (Box 6, Folder 4)